taaz.com 2014-12-14

# TAAZ Privacy Policy

Taaz, Inc. (the “Company”) has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site www.taaz.com and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile applications. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

Taaz, Inc. complies with the U.S.–E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Taaz, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Taaz, Inc. certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

You post any Content (as that term is defined in the Company's [Terms of Use](http://www.taaz.com/terms-of-use.html)) on the Website at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that Content you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your Content. 

Any improper collection or misuse of Content or other information accessible on the Website is a violation of the Company's Terms of Use and should be reported to [tou@taaz.com](http://www.taaz.com/tou@taaz.com). 

### What Other Personal Information Does Company Display or Collect?

This Privacy Policy covers Company's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Company gathers when you are accessing the Website, www.taaz.com, and when you use our services. When you use the Website, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, and transmit information through various channels. The information we gather from users enables us to personalize and improve our services, and to allow our users to set up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with Company and other users through the Website. In most cases, we retain such information so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. In addition to the foregoing, we collect the following types of information from our users. 

### Personal Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on the Website. The types of Personal Information collected may include, without limitation, your name, email address, photograph, physical descriptions and personal interests. You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain information, products and services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new features. You may modify or remove your Personal Information identified below at any time by logging into your account and accessing features to edit your profile and account information. 

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our Website, add a friend to your profile, or share a makeover with a friend we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the Website. Company stores this information to send this invitation, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at tou@taaz.comto request that we remove this information from our database. 

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), and to send participants an email newsletter. 

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to Company or on the Website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at tou@taaz.com . 

### Email Communications:

We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from Company by using clear gifs in our HTML-based emails. Company uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. We also compare our user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please follow the unsubscribe instructions in the emails. 

### What About Cookies?

We use cookies to remember users’ settings and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Taaz Inc. and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers (e.g. Ad networks). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

**Log Files** \- As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 or Flash to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

### Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising

Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies or web beacons. These cookies or web beacons allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Company and does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any advertisers. If you do not wish to have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

We use Google AdSense to publish ads on this site. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

### Will Company Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives?

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. 

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include sending email, analyzing data, and providing user services. Unless we tell you differently, Company's agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

User Profiles: User profile information including, without limitation, users' name, email address, photographs, physical descriptions and personal interests, may be used to facilitate and provide your requested services within the Website and/or your request for Company's services or applications through third party websites. Any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your display name may be displayed to other users when you upload images or videos or send messages through the Website and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Any images, captions, physical descriptions, personal interests or other content that you submit to the Websites may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

Communication About the Website or in Response to User Requests: As part of the Website and our services, you will receive from Company email and other communication relating to your use of the Website or your profile. You acknowledge and agree that by posting information of the Website or otherwise using the Website, Company and its agents may send you email, contact you or engage in other communication that they determine in their sole discretion relate to your profile or use of the Website. Company may use a user's email address (or telephone number for text and multimedia messaging) to send updates, a newsletter or other news regarding the Website or Company services. 

Promotional Offers: We may send offers to certain users on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send us an email to tou@taaz.com 

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Company, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Company goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Company may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. We will notify you via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

Protection of Company and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be given the option to prevent the sharing of this information. 

### Is Personal Information About me Secure?

Your Company account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

Company endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private by following generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, Company cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. For additional information about the security measures Company uses in connection with the Website, please contact us at [tou@taaz.com](mailto:tou@taaz.com). 

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at tou@taaz.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Does Site Have Links to Third Party Websites?

The Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Company. Company is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on this Website. When you use "Share This" to bookmark and share our products and site, you will be taken to a third party site. Please note that these third party sites' privacy policies govern the collection and use of the information collected on those sites. Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post information to public areas on the Website or any other public forums, such information can be accessed by the public. 

### What Personal Information Can I Access?

Company allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating and deleting that information. This list will change as the Website changes. You may currently access the following information: 

  * Account information
  * User profile
  * User friends' list
  * User preferences and
  * Photographs and content in your account

### What Other Choices Do I Have?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain Company features. 

You are able to add, update or delete certain information on pages, such as those listed in the "What Personal Information Can I Access" section above. If you would like to access your personal information in order to correct, update, or delete it, you may also contact us directly at tou@taaz.com. Requests for access will be responded to within 30 days of the request. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. 

You may request deletion of your Company account by sending an email to our webmaster at tou@taaz.com. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

### Public Member Directory

We will list you in our publicly accessible member directory. If you wish to request removal of your information from our directory, you can contact us at [taaz-support@taaz.com](mailto:taaz-support@taaz.com) . 

### Public Profiles

The profile you create on our site will be publically accessible unless otherwise indicated. You may change the privacy settings of your profile through your account portal. 

### Facebook Connect

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. This service will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network 

### Social Media Widgets

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

### Testimonial

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at tou@taaz.com. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Company may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you via email or by posting an announcement on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted. 

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at TAAZ.com, please send us a detailed message to [tou@taaz.com](mailto:tou@taaz.com) or 

Taaz, Inc.  
4330 La Jolla Village Drive, Suite 340  
San Diego, CA 92122

We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

_Effective date: November 3, 2014_
